Thank you for watching!
Ana channel applause
Crackle, crackle, crackle, crackle
Crackle, crackle, crackle, crackle.
We're here at Sea World.
What are we doing here this time?
Well, this is a summer vacation project for busy ano-chan.
I'm hoping that you will enjoy the aquarium with a guest attendant.
Have we been here before?
Yes, actually, we came here 2 years ago in 2021 for an uncut location shoot.
One and a half minutes to 10 minutes.
What? We don't have time.
I'm gonna lose my pants.
Maybe we can do it all this time.
Follow the cameraman.
It's like we're floating.
Here's a picture.
What's that?
There it is.
They're both taking pictures.
Here.
There he is.
I'm you.
There's a picture over there.
There's a picture.
I have to take a picture.
I don't think I got a good look at it then.
I hope you can take the time to look at it all today.
Okay.
Now, please invite our guest.
Our guest this time is this person.
Pleased to meet you.
Nice to meet you. - Nice to meet you.
Who is it?
Hi, I'm Nusuburanko.Hi, my name is Nasuburanko.
I look forward to working with you.
Thank you very much.
That channel
Yes, ma'am.
Hello. - Hello.
It's nice to see you.
I've got an anterior crease.
Drive.
Horse racing.
They were doing horse racing, too.
There was a lot of buzz.
It was the number one teleplay.
I was number one.
It's the number one project.
That's outrageous.
This is comparable.
Clearly.
It's a clear numerical comparison.
We're in the same class.
Good luck with that.
You know very well.
I'm sorry.
By the way, I...
I originally met Ano in a project called
Longha's Lovemageddon project.
If there were no other members on a deserted island, who would you choose?
A man and a woman as a feeling couple.
I see.
I was already in the project.
Ano-chan in the "well" position
Ano-chan at the well
Anochan!
Boom! I said
Ano, you were in the well position, Botasan.
I'm sorry.Sorry.
That's not what I meant at all.
My arrow went right in front of it.
It went right in front of it.
It's gone.
I'll see you later.
It's like a short drama about a horror project.
A short drama.
And Ano...
I'm going to write a one-woman show.
I'm also writing a project
That kind of project.
That's great.
You've been involved in a lot of things.
So you're involved in a lot of things.
As a male trapeze artist
Yes.
That's what you remember.
What do you mean, what do you mean, what do you mean, who can use the space like that?
She didn't say "papa," but she was hot.
She was our mentor on Yamasato-san's show about 5 years ago... the guy with the glasses...
Boober, I'm...
I called her out on twitter when she shined a light in our hearts.
It's not that I don't like him.
He saved us from slipping a little with his boo boo shisugo.
The one who made it happen.
I remember how you saved my life...
It's been a long time since I've seen you... and it's nice to meet you... and today we've got the guys from UplanCon.
I've been here before with a couple of the guys from the male upranch group.
Boo-Boo was part of a live show, so I know him pretty well.
I'm going to start with the orca performance because of the time constraints.
I'm glad to hear that you're going to see the orca performance, because I'd really like to go, even if the sun is a little too strong.
All right, let's go!
When the combo is different, it's almost like you're desperate
I think so too!I agree.
Because we all won this.
I'd like to give you something to look forward to.
I'll make it as fun as possible for you. Rap scars.
I love you
Rekiko
Sandy
Good, you're a desperate fool.
You're really
You're really doing a great job.
That channel is so harsh, isn't it?
It's so egregious.
Like this.
Oh, but it's starting already?
It's hot, but...
But I'd better hold on to the water coming.
Is it going to be like this?
It's definitely going to get water here, right?
Just this much.
There are days when you just have to do this.
Yeah, yeah.
It's scary.
I'm taking off my shoes, too.
I'm told to stay barefoot.
The preparation for getting wet is amazing.Have you ever seen it?
No, I haven't.
No?
Well, to begin with, the car lot itself is
Nagoya Port Aquarium and Kamagawa Sea World
Nagoya Port Aquarium and Kamakawa Sea World.
That's why it's very valuable.
It is very precious.
I saw Kurumachi for the first time.
First time to see Kurumachi?
Yes, it was.Yeah, I saw it the other day.
I saw you the other day.
Me?
Fifteen minutes.
Oh, I see, you saw it in the 15 minutes.
I didn't see it.
I don't remember seeing it.
No, I'm sure.
Here it comes.
Oh, oh...
They're here.
Killer whale performance. Oh, wow. The lady gave a big yelp.
What? What do we do now?
Whoa!
Wow!
It's huge!
Wow! It's huge.
It's powerful. I saw it here. At such a distance.
I've never seen anything like this. It's amazing. Dynamic.
That's great. Thank you.
Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you.
I'm back.
What?
One hand this time.
Whoa!
Closer, closer, closer.
Wow!
Oh, my God!
Is this happening? What?
Wait a minute!Wait a minute!
Wait a minute!
You know, I totally...
I totally noticed!
I thought it was more...
No, now wait a minute, now...
Is it in the water?
What?
Everybody's in. Oh, my God.
Like this?
Whoo-hoo!
I knew it!
It's not as bad as I thought...
It's more than I thought it would be.
It's totally, totally salty.
Hey!
It tastes like salt.
It's the ocean that tastes like salt.
All the little bits of clothing that were showing are done.
One and Ding.
I'm all done around here, but you
One blow.
Here we go again?
That's great.
Oh, my.
Here it comes, here it comes.
Another close-up.
Oh!
It's huge!
Aah!
He's so cute!
In black and white.
Beautiful black and white.
Oh!Oh my!
That's a laugh!
That's awesome!
That's so cool!
Cool filming!
Sakatate.
That was just Sakatate.
No way!
Wait a minute!
Excuse me!
Um...
Are you all right now?
Oh, my God.
Oh!
Sour.
There you go.
Meow.
Cheer up.
Hey, guys.
Oh, my gosh!That's great.
Rem have
Azi iji
Very nice!
Schön
Is it good?
Oh, my God.
Hey, even the salt is great!
What is this?
Wait, what? What just happened?
Oh, my God, the cameras just stopped.
Camera's off.
The camera's stopped.
Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
What's happening?
Oh, my God. Are you okay?
Just fine.
Give me a dry towel.
Are you okay?
I'm fine. I'm fine.
Did you break the camera?
How much did it break?
I did.
R
whit
Yes, I saw the performance in the car lot, and you mentioned a few things one by one.
There were a lot of troubles. First of all, two cameras died.
We're working on restoring them now... with a double dryer...
I'm currently in the process of restoring them, but I've lost all the cameras.
I'm sorry, but I've got to get a picture of you on my phone case.
I've got a pension... I've got a pension...
I've got my pension, and... and... and... and... and... and... and... and... and... and... and... and... and... and... and... and... and... and we're in the boat.
I'm wearing this at first, then I changed over there, and now I'm not going, but I'm going to look at fishI was wearing this at first, then I changed over there, and now I'm not going because I want to see the fish.
I was wearing this, and then I changed over there and now I'm not going because I'm going to see the fish
I'm in my pajamas, but that's how I came in my pie, and here's my outfit, and here's Moto-chan's outfit.
I'm sure it's a tough fight, but it was great!
I'm sure it was great!
I'm not going to jump, but I'm going to jump!
I've been waiting for it all day... but here it is... there it is... there it is...
Look, look, look... it's him... and I can hear what he's shouting...
I can see that...
I'm talking about the weather.
He's underwater, so he's swimming now, and he's lying down here, and the long, thin one is under his feet.
And this one here is a little bit chunky, and this one is a seal, and this one is a different kind.
I think they're sesame style, too.
Sesame style? What do you mean "sesame"? It's not a sesame sauce.
What's the one that doesn't look like a sesame seed?
There's another one called "zeni-shaped seal". The old zeni.
It's got an open center with a zeni-like pattern. Is that the zeni-shaped seal?
That's the zeni-shaped seal? - That's right. There are zeni-shaped and sesame-like ones.
There's no "zeni-shaped" seal up there.
That's a Zenigata.
Look at the pattern... it's a doughnut-shaped pattern.
Donut-shaped burn... that's what it looks like.
It's not a motif of your cave. It's not a cave motif.
Zeni-shaped seal, the money one. Zeni-shaped seal.
That's the sesame seed duster. It's a sesame seed.
What's this? That's a sea lion. That's a California sea lion.
You know... sea lions are like otaries and fur seals.
Next time... the ear tabs on their ears...
They're sharp, like the sea lions.
Seals don't have ear tabs.
Let's go next time. I've lost interest.
Let's go next. I've lost interest.
He said he was sorry about the ears.
There's no such thing as "I'm sorry about your ears.
If I'm right...
If I'm right, this is a very interesting monster.This is a very interesting monster.
I wonder if it's here.
Look at this... do you know it?
I don't know. It's a walrus. A walrus.
What's a walrus doing?
Fangs, fangs, fangs, fangs, fangs, fangs.
That's a little scary.
A little scary.
That's great. That's a little scary.
The walrus, you see, has all kinds of sensory organs in its whiskers.
It's so sensitive, it can feel everything.
I'm fine. I'm fine. I'm totally fine.
Walrus.
Walrus is talking to you.
"Hello.
He's looking at me, obviously.
He's obviously looking at me, even though it's closing time.
The pastor is a monarch, so if there's someone around, he'll come and check on them.
How old is he?
The one that just turned 16 is almost an adult.
The other two are still young, still growing.
They're going to get bigger.
The biggest one is 10 years old.
She's about three meters long.
He's 3 meters long and weighs 900 kilograms.
He's 900 kilos, but he'll be up to 1500 kilos when he's older.
He's still young.
Fresh.
Let's go.
He's here.
What is it?
Steller's sea lion, the largest species in the sea lion family.
I've heard of Steller's sea lions.
They're called sea lions.
He's sleeping.Sleeping.
I'm up.
He's awake.
He's totally whimpering.
It's true, this Steller's sea lion has such a guttural cry.
It's said to be so loud that you can hear it for miles.
It's said to be so loud that it can be heard for miles.
Like an uncle waking up from sleep.
But... maybe... it's still tiny.
And she's a female.
I see.
Only Steller's sea lions here?
Only Steller's sea lions.
Their voices are amazing.
Even the females have a great, great, great cry.
They're so cute.
The way she rests... with her eyes closed.
She's resting.
So cute!
So cute.
I didn't get to see him this much last time.
Oh, good, good.
I saw it from the side.
Oh, I was running here, so I could see.
I was running.
Just a little bit more.
Where?
Right here.
Here? Here? Here?
We've been going around for 15 minutes.
Yeah.
What a waste of time.
It's a great project.
Yeah.
Perrot is cute.
He looks a bit like a dog.You look a bit like a dog.
He's cute.
Maybe he's cute.
He's licking his lips.
There you go.
Let's continue.
This time, take your time.
Oh, I think that's it.
Look at this.
It's a dolphin.
Dolphins?
A Pacific white-sided dolphin.
A Pacific white-sided dolphin?
Yes, a Pacific white-sided dolphin.
Oh, this one? It's tiny.
It's a little bit small.
Oh, it's cute.
What? Look so close.
Oh, heh.
Cute dolphin.
Why is it a Pacific white-sided dolphin?
Wow, they're so small!
Is that what a Pacific white-sided dolphin is?
Because its dorsal fin looks like a sickle?
I knew it!
Its dorsal fin looks like a sickle.
The dorsal fin is shaped like a sickle, so it's called a Pacific white-sided dolphin.
I see...
The keeper told us.
Oh, he showed his face!
Finish your sweetness!
Oh, it's making a sound!
He's saying something
It's true, he's a duck.
What's that? It's quacking.
They're saying something.He's saying something.
But maybe they're communicating maybe.
Wow, cool.
That's cool.
They fly so low, the Pacific white-sided dolphins.
You must have gotten wet earlier.
That's true.
I'm just saying, that's not how we do things around here.
I'm just trying to be nice.
That was really fast.
How fast do you swim?
40, 50 kilometers.
Wow!
Wow, that's cool.
It's so cool to be fast!
I like the fast ones.
I like fast.
Whatever.
I like to run fast.
Wow!
Beautiful.
It's so smooth.
Are you sleeping?
Sleeping.
They swim in their sleep.
What kind of dolphins?
They close their right eye and rest their left brain.
Or they close their left eye and rest their right brain.
They do that.
There are so many dangers in the ocean.
Oh, my God.
Your eyes are open.
That's great.
That's a very slow turn.
That's great.Good for you.
Penguin.
Wait, penguins, they're real!
Humboldt penguins.
So cute!
So cool!
So many penguins, so many penguins!
They're so colorful!
What's up, what's up, what's up
They're all here.
Hello, hello, hello.
The colors are so nice.
What's going on?
What are you doing?
It's for the choir competition.
Chorus competition.
They're so cute!
They're all over the place!
Penguins are so cute!
Penguins are cute
Humboldt penguins
I wonder why they gathered here
They looked so surprised
There aren't many people here at this time of night.
at this time of the day
It's like they were surprised.
I'm sorry if I startled you.
I'm sorry.
You don't have to hide. You can come out.
I know TV.
You know what I'm talking about.
It's so... it's so... it's like...
It's like you're so surprised that you're coming out.
One hole for each of you.
Private room.Private rooms
private room
Like a list
List System
So cute!
And we got to see penguins.
Good, good, good.
It's too peaceful.
Too tranquil.
That channel.
I always say I want to do something peaceful.
And then some loud guy comes in.
I can't relax.
Mr. Ikeya...
Like Mr. Ikeya...
That's why I'm glad.
Today was totally normal.
I'm just going to go see the aquarium.
I'm glad.
You don't come here often in your private time? The aquarium.
I don't come here at all.
I mean, I'd like to ask a simple person...
Please tell me you're not a simple person.
What do you mean by "confess your feelings"?
What do you mean by "confess"?
Why do you want to go?
What made you decide to go to the aquarium?
What happened and with whom?
Oh, my God.
Do you have kids?
No.
You seem like you have a lot of kids.
No, I don't.
There's the scarecrow.
I don't have kids.
I'm taking care of them.He's feeding her.
I just feel like I'm there.
I just feel like a dad, that's all.
I don't have kids.
I don't have a wife.
He looks like he's got a wife.
I mean, I look like I could have a wife.
Don't say that when you're getting to the second half of the show.
It's like...
I just realized...
I just noticed.
I just noticed it.
I just saw it.
He looks like a dad.
He looks so much like a dad.
He's not here.
He's not here?
He's not here? What are you gonna do?
I don't know.
But we could go on a date.
Or to the aquarium.
While you're looking at it.
Yeah.
Like that.
If we have something in common.
It would be nice.
I don't know.
He's a comedian.
I'm sure he's very funny.
Dating a comedian...
It's never like that.
Sometimes you have to put it down completely.
That's for sure.
With a comedian.
You're so beautiful.It's so beautiful.
Like the aquarium tank.
The layout.
The coral reefs.
It's different every day, isn't it?
Yeah, but...
I don't think they change it every day.
So that it's fun to look at.
That's what I'm particular about.
Each aquarium has its own.
I like fish, too.
Oh, I see.
I'm using a pencil case with fish on it.
And my key chain is a fish key chain.
That's nice.
But I don't know...
I like it because it's dead.
Dead?
Illustration.
The pattern.
As a character.
Like, as a character.
But that's okay.
Even if they're realistic.
I can look at them because they're not moving.
I don't see them moving very often.
I can't wait to see it today.
I want to see moving fish.
I want to see a fish tank.
Yeah, I want to see the tank.
I want to see a big aquarium.
Clam, clam, clam.
It's so big!
It's going to escape!
There's a turtle trying to escape.Tortoise trying to escape.
The newcomer trying to escape.
The turtle.
It's trying to get out.
But it's amazing.
There's a hot spring like this.
Yes, there are.
It looks like it's connected to the ocean.
Like a resort.
So do sea turtles.
But I really hate people who put that kind of thing
I really hate people who put that on Instagram.
You don't have to say anything.
It's okay if you don't like it.
I know it's just a secret.
I won't go.
I'm not going.
This is right in front of you.
I think it's a red sea turtle.
I didn't know sea turtles were this big.
This is a green sea turtle.
That's a big one.
There's a red one and a blue one.
What? Dandelion.
Red sea turtles...
It's kind of a mess.
It's a little big-headed.
I think so.
It's a little...
It's not a very cozy profile.
It's not fluffy.
Sir...
You're getting complaints.
You know what?
Don't give me vague information.Don't put in vague information.
Okay, so the red sea turtles have slightly larger heads.
It's a little big-headed.
Tell them apart.
Big head.
It's hard for a layman to tell them apart.
This one has a big head.
It's a little big.
Not too big.
It's big for some people.
Some people might say they're big.
Maybe so, but...
Green turtles are...
The green sea turtle
The red sea turtle
If you have a small head...
Will be a green sea turtle?
That's what I'm talking about.
This, this, this.
What? This is blue?
This is a little bit...
What is it? What's a little bit of that?
This little something.
This is a red sea turtle.
What about the blue?
The blue one.
Uh...
They're in the back.
What's that?
He's cute.
But... they're both endangered.
Both red sea turtles and blue sea turtles.
It's important to protect them.
Let's go.
Let's go.Let's go.
Subscribe to Amachan Channel!
undefined